that wants to know what is the value of
x and what is the value of each of these
other three angles we can do this the
sum of the interior angles of any
four-sided figure is always 360 degrees
so we can just say this angle plus this
angle plus this angle plus this angle is
equal to 360. and then X Plus 3x plus 2X
is equal to 6X and then all these
numbers are going to combine to give us
negative 2154 and it's still equal to
360. if we add 2154 to both sides we get
6X on the left hand side and 25 14 on
the right hand side divide both sides by
6 and we get x equals 419 and we can
plug the X in up here so now that we
know what x is we can plug that in for
each of these other angles copy down the
values for each of the angles plug in
419 for the X's 3 times 419 is 1257 and
2 times 419 is 838 419 minus 352 is 67.
1257 minus 1189 is 68. and 838 minus 768
is 70. how exciting